{
    "id": "905336b30d454e63aee57e2e61dfb8b4",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. the manager in the afternoon.",
            "description": "We use the present continuous to talk about a future event that is already planned.",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "am seeing",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a873e8f3007f4cfa9405bdb4be03775b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… his voice.",
            "description": "The verb like is hardly ever used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "a liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cade4e1bbe9d42fdb6d15859a38504c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I called him because I …………………………. to talk.",
            "description": "Want is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "wanted",
                "was wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b95e7341e89c4364b136a3401e6f4486"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ……………………………. hard.",
            "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about actions or situations that are going on at the moment of speaking. ",
            "answers": [
                "rains",
                "is raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "98e3d3ea303844fba168dc7ce7595a66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. that education should be free for all.",
            "description": "Believe is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "believe",
                "am believing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b35ee9b1b84846a0a2c96cf16a6011ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. that we are committing a mistake.",
            "description": "When feel means have an opinion, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "691d2fe8e9d54263a3cfe46b49300099"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. how to ride a bicycle.",
            "description": "Know is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "am knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e48837144dfc48f9a4bf2bc9808d1901"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… my holidays right now.",
            "description": "The present continuous is used to talk about ongoing situations.",
            "answers": [
                "enjoy",
                "am enjoying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c44d6a3792ae4249966e427b2484aa9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… when they arrived.",
            "description": "The past continuous is used to talk about the longer background action that was in progress when another action occurred.",
            "answers": [
                "slept",
                "is sleeping",
                "was sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d74791ec42ad4c98a31a99e24bff7238"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………………… difficult now.",
            "description": "Look is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "looks",
                "is looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24b8205f7e65476c95e5080546a887f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………… to a hill tribe.",
            "description": "Belong is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "belongs",
                "is belonging"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9d28591ebe7404487aa14bd7b0422e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. 50 kg last month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was weighing",
                "weighed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "828c7d72dbbc479f9986a5570b9c5964"
        }
    ]
}